quiz2 = {
    1: {
        "question": "Mis on 1x1?",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    2: {
        "question": "Mis on 1x2?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    3: {
        "question": "Mis on 1x3?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    4: {
        "question": "Mis on 1x4?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    5: {
        "question": "Mis on 1x5?",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    6: {
        "question": "Mis on 1x6?",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    7: {
        "question": "Mis on 1x7?",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    8: {
        "question": "Mis on 1x8?",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    9: {
        "question": "Mis on 1x9?",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    10: {
        "question": "Mis on 1x10?",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    11: {
        "question": "Mis on 2x1?",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    12: {
        "question": "Mis on 2x2?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    13: {
        "question": "Mis on 2x3?",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    14: {
        "question": "Mis on 2x4?",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    15: {
        "question": "Mis on 2x5?",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    16: {
        "question": "Mis on 2x6?",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    17: {
        "question": "Mis on 2x7?",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    18: {
        "question": "Mis on 2x8?",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    19: {
        "question": "Mis on 2x9?",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    20: {
        "question": "Mis on 2x10?",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    21: {
        "question": "Mis on 3x1?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    22: {
        "question": "Mis on 3x2?",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    23: {
        "question": "Mis on 3x3?",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    24: {
        "question": "Mis on 3x4?",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    25: {
        "question": "Mis on 3x5?",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    26: {
        "question": "Mis on 3x6?",
        "answer": "18"
    },
    27: {
        "question": "Mis on 3x7?",
        "answer": "21"
    },
    28: {
        "question": "Mis on 3x8?",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    29: {
        "question": "Mis on 3x9?",
        "answer": "27"
    },
    30: {
        "question": "Mis on 3x10?",
        "answer": "30"
    },
    31: {
        "question": "Mis on 4x1?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    32: {
        "question": "Mis on 4x2?",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    33: {
        "question": "Mis on 4x3?",
        "answer": "12"
    },
    34: {
        "question": "Mis on 4x4?",
        "answer": "16"
    },
    35: {
        "question": "Mis on 4x5?",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    36: {
        "question": "Mis on 4x6?",
        "answer": "24"
    },
    37: {
        "question": "Mis on 4x7?",
        "answer": "28"
    },
    38: {
        "question": "Mis on 4x8?",
        "answer": "32"
    },
    39: {
        "question": "Mis on 4x9?",
        "answer": "36"
    },
    40: {
        "question": "Mis on 4x10?",
        "answer": "40"
    },
    41: {
        "question": "Mis on 5x1?",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    42: {
        "question": "Mis on 5x2?",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    43: {
        "question": "Mis on 5x3?",
        "answer": "15"
    },
    44: {
        "question": "Mis on 5x4?",
        "answer": "20"
    },
    45: {
        "question": "Mis on 5x5?",
        "answer": "25"
    },
    46: {
        "question": "Mis on 5x6?",
        "answer": "30"
    },
    47: {
        "question": "Mis on 5x7?",
        "answer": "35"
    },
    48: {
        "question": "Mis on 5x8?",
        "answer": "40"
    },
    49: {
        "question": "Mis on 5x9?",
        "answer": "45"
    },
    50: {
        "question": "Mis on 5x10?",
        "answer": "50"
    }
}
